[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these songs does Cameron Diaz perform in the 1997 romantic comedy My Best Friends Wedding?", "correct_answer": "I Just Dont Know What to Do with Myself", "incorrect_answers": ["Tell Him", "I Say A Little Prayer (For You)", "The Way You Look Tonight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Peace Treaty between Jordan and Israel was signed near Eilat. In what year did this happen?", "correct_answer": "October, 1994", "incorrect_answers": ["October, 2004", "October,1968", "October, 1975"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Marco Antonio Muniz is the real name of this actor.", "correct_answer": "Marc Antony", "incorrect_answers": ["Miguel A. Nunez", "Emelio Estevez", "Antonio Banderas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the film directed by Martin Campbell, produced by Doug Claybourne and David Foster, with Antonio Banderas as the main character?", "correct_answer": "The Mask of Zorro", "incorrect_answers": ["Amores Perros", "All About My Mother", "Y Tu Mama Tambien"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the movie Champagne, which tells the story of a young woman forced to get a job after her father tells her he has lost all his money?", "correct_answer": "Alfred Hitchcock", "incorrect_answers": ["Ingmar Bergman", "Martin Scorsese", "Woody Allen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these dinosaurs was bigger than a dog?", "correct_answer": "Triceratops", "incorrect_answers": ["Saltopus", "Parvicursor", "Microraptor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Alaska used to be part of Russia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This leader, who ruled the Holy Roman Empire from 1792 until 1806, is known as the last Holy Roman Emperor.", "correct_answer": "Francis II", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilhelm XII of Saxony", "Francis Ferdinand I of Austria", "Wilhelm I of Prussia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first song transmitted from space to Earth?", "correct_answer": "Happy Birthday", "incorrect_answers": ["Space Oddity", "The I Love Lucy Theme Song", "There has been no song transmitted from space to Earth."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these mountains is not a volcano?", "correct_answer": "Mount Aspiring", "incorrect_answers": ["Mauna Kea", "Mount St. Helens", "Mount Vesuvius"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest planet in our solar system. It is most famous for its Great Red Spot.", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Neptune", "Saturn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These particles form light, as you see it.", "correct_answer": "Photons", "incorrect_answers": ["Electrons", "Quarks", "Leptons"]}]